grantassist.com 2013-09-09

# GrantAssist.com - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitor's personally identifiable information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our site. 

What Information We Collect and How We Use It 

**Personally Identifiable Information  
 **

When you place an order for products or services we collect certain types of personally identifiable information including contact information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number; and if you choose to provide it, other personal information, such as a credit card number. 

We use this information to process requests for products and services by way of customer support for your guaranteed satisfaction. We also use collected information to communicate with you, such as to notify you (through e-mails and newsletters) about updates to products, to send you order confirmations, or to provide you with important product warranty or safety information. 

In addition, we use contact information you provide to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you, by means of e-mail or through our newsletter, additional products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

**Sharing of Your information  
**  
Protecting personally identifiable information about our partners and clients is an essential cornerstone of our business. We share and disclose such information only as described below. www.GrantAssist.com sends very limited personally identifiable information about you (such as your email address or phone number) to other companies or people: 1) when we determine that the information will be used in a way that will greatly benefit the consumer. We enjoy assisting our clients with the best quality and economical information to assist them in their financial education; 2) when we need to share your information with third parties, such as banks and credit card processors, to provide the product or service you have requested; 3) in connection with products and services offered by www.GrantAssist.com business partners and/or companies who work on behalf of www.GrantAssist.com to provide a product or service to you; 4) it is appropriate to comply with law; 5) it is necessary to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our Terms of Service and / or other applicable agreements; or 6) it is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of www.GrantAssist.com, our users, or others, which may include the exchange of information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction. In the event that www.GrantAssist.com is acquired, customer account information may be one of the transferred assets. 

Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect it in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for www.GrantAssist.com. 

In addition, we will share aggregated demographic information with our Strategic Partners. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

Our Collection of Personally Identifiable Information Through a Third-party Web Site 

To provide you with content and service, we have relationships with many of the best service and content companies. As a result of these relationships, you can access www.GrantAssist.com through a third-party Web site. You can recognize most of the www.GrantAssist.com pages on these third-party sites by looking for the joint branding of www.GrantAssist.com and a third-party company. For example, if you see a logo on the page that says "Powered by www.GrantAssist.com," you are on a co-branded page. 

Whenever you provide registration information on a co-branded page, that data may be shared with the third-party site through which you access www.GrantAssist.com. If personally identifiable information may be provided to such a third party, we will inform you at the point of collection and provide you with an opportunity to tell us not to share your personally identifiable information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as this Notice does not cover their use of information 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
**  
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS X) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., AOL, PeoplePC). 

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our service pages and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze service usage. 

**Legal Process/Disclaimer  
**  
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request 

**Choices/Opt Out  
**  
If you prefer not to receive marketing information or wish to fully deactivate your account information from us, simply let us know by sending a letter via certified mail to www.GrantAssist.com at 12316 Rosebriar Ln, Riverton, UT 84065. Please note that even if you chose to opt out of www.GrantAssist.com's marketing, we will continue to send you important service-related communications (e.g., order confirmation or product safety information). However, these are not promotional in nature. 

**Cookies  
**  
To enhance your experience with our site, we use "cookies." Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. 

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you will still be able to use our site. 

**Links  
**  
In addition, our site contains links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Our privacy policy does not cover these third parties' use of information. Visitors should consult the other companies' and sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

**Security  
**  
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

All information submitted is protected by our secure server, which automatically encrypts your personally identifiable information so that it cannot be read while traveling over the Internet. 

**Reviewing Your Information  
**  
If you would like to review and update or correct the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you online, or if no longer wish to continue your service with us, simply submit your request via our Contact Us form. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Notification of Changes  
**  
If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a materially different manner from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you directly (e.g., via e-mail). You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. However, if you have opted out of communication with the site then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. 

**Contact Us  
**  
If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us using our online Contact Us form.
